orlygift.com 2019-06-11

# orlygift - Indie Steam games for free

###  **Orlygift - Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which **www.orlygift.com** collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the **www.orlygift.com** website (“Site.") By viewing, accessing, using or browsing the Website, or by registering as a member of the Service (as defined herein), you agree to this privacy policy and the Terms of Service of said web property as a binding legal agreement between you and **www.orlygift.com** , without limitation or qualification. 

**Personal identification information**

**www.orlygift.com** keeps track of non-personally identifiable information such as the IP address of the User’s computer, time of access, browser type and files downloaded to gather usage statistics for its web site. IP addresses are not associated with other information about a user, but only indicate general visitor navigation patterns. **www.orlygift.com** website has embedded tags that allow some third party entities such as [Quantcast](http://www.quantcast.com/docs/display/legal/Privacy+Policy), [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics/), and/or similar services to collect non-personally identifiable usage statistics. 

**Submission and Processing of Information**

When you subscribe or sign up to the Website, **www.orlygift.com** may ask you for certain personally identifiable information. This personally identifiable information may include information that can be used to identify or contact you, such as your name and email address. You must agree to the Terms of Service of this website before making any comments or leaving any reviews on any posting. 

**User Postings**

Except as otherwise expressly described in this Privacy Policy, this policy only addresses the use and disclosure of Personal Information and other information we collect from you. In the course of your use of the Website, including when you create a profile on the Website, you may elect to post or otherwise disclose information about yourself and others, which may include Personal Information or other personally identifiable information. You may also elect to communicate with others or upload content such as photographs. Such postings are governed by our Terms of Service. Whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information on publicly-viewable web pages, that information will be publicly available and can be collected or used by others. Such postings may also appear on other websites or when searches are executed on the subject of your posting. 

Furthermore, although www.orlygift.com restricts access to portions of the Website to members of the Service, since the Service is offered through and accessible through a number of other websites in addition to the Website, any information that you post to the Website for access by members of the Website may be searchable and available to users of the Service who access it via different websites from the Website. You may also receive unsolicited messages from other parties as a result of such disclosure. Such activities are beyond the control of Www.orlygift.com and this Privacy Policy. You should therefore exercise discretion and extreme caution when disclosing any Personal Information or other information when using the Website or the Service. 

**Third Party Websites**

The Website may contain links to other websites. www.orlygift.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such websites. It is the User's responsibility to review the privacy policies at those websites to confirm that they are acceptable prior to use. A link does not constitute an endorsement of the content, viewpoint or accuracy of such websites. 

**Marketing Communications**

If you have used the Website before, it is possible that **www.orlygift.com** has data about you already and it is being used to contact you about offers, events, items or related activities. If you are an existing customer, **www.orlygift.com** will continue to keep you informed unless you revoke your consent via the procedures set forth below. 

If you are a new user, **www.orlygift.com** will give you the choice (for example, once you have subscribed or signed up) whether or not you want to receive emails regarding future offers, events and new services or related activities. www.orlygift.com will not bombard you with emails, but Www.orlygift.com, with your consent, would like to keep you informed of any developments on the Website. 

If you have consented to receive such information, you may always revoke that consent at any time by deleting your account. 

**Confidentiality and Security of Personal Information**

Transmission of data and information via the Website is not a secure or encrypted transmission method for sending your Personal Information, unless otherwise indicated on the Website. Accordingly, your attention is drawn to the fact that any information and personal data carried over the Internet is not secure. Personal Information may be intercepted, lost, redirected, corrupted, changed and accessed by other people. 

Nevertheless, www.orlygift.com is committed to using all reasonable efforts to protect Personal Information collected through the Website against unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Consequently, we limit employees' access to Personal Information collected through the Website to only those employees who need access to the information in the performance of their official duties. 

In addition, we set strict security standards to prevent any unauthorized access to your Personal Information once we have received it and wherever possible we will use adequate security software and working procedures to ensure the security of your personal data. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain accuracy, and ensure proper use of Personal Information, we have employed physical, electronic, and managerial processes to safeguard and secure the Personal Information we collect online. These measures include limiting the number of people who have physical access to www.orlygift.com database servers, as well as electronic security systems and password protections which guard against unauthorized access. 

Data in our Logs. When you use Orlygift or go to a webpage or use an app that has Orlygift features (like our “Share It” button), our system automatically records that information (“data in our logs”) including information that your internet browser sends whenever you search a website or your mobile application sends when you’re using it going to and from different applications. The data in our logs may also include your IP address, the address of the most recent web pages you’ve visited that had Orlygift features, browser type and settings, the date and time of your request, how you used Orlygift, and cookie data. 

**Disclosure of Personal Information**

We may disclose your Personal Information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries and our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries. We may disclose your Personal Information to third parties if you have consented to such disclosure. In addition, we may disclose or provide access to your Personal Information to third parties without your consent: 

if we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your Personal Information to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets; 

if www.orlygift.com or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case Personal Information held by it about its customers will, in most instances, be one of the transferred assets; 

if we ask a third party to carry out data analysis, cleansing and/or market research on our behalf; 

for the purpose of validating the identity of the user and/or conducting background checks; or 

if we have a good faith belief that we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation (such as in connection with a law enforcement request, judicial proceeding, court order or legal process), or in order to enforce or apply our policy or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Www.orlygift.com, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

**Children's Online Privacy**

It is important to Www.orlygift.com that parents and guardians have control over what information is collected from their children online and how such information is or may be used. The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 ("COPPA") imposes restrictions on commercial websites, including ours. It is our policy to be compliant with the requirements of COPPA and not to solicit or collect information about or from children age 13 and under. 

Beyond the requirements of COPPA, we require that individuals be age 18 or over to register as a member of the Service and thus it is our policy not to solicit or collect information about or from anyone under the age of 18. Users are cautioned, however, that absent a clear indication an online communication has been submitted by a person under age 18, the collection of Personal Information submitted to the Website will be treated as though it was submitted by an adult, and may, unless exempted from access by federal or state law, be subject to public access. 

In the event that www.orlygift.com receives an online communication clearly indicating that it has been submitted by a person under the age of 18, under no circumstances will any Personal Information be published on the Website, be used for a purpose not intended by its sender or shared with third parties. 

If you or your company would like more information about COPPA, please visit the Federal Trade Commission's official COPPA page at [www.ftc.gov](http://www.ftc.gov/). 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy and Transfers of Ownership**

You agree that if we transfer ownership or management of the Website or Www.orlygift.com to a third party we may also transfer your Personal Information and any other data or information you have provided to us to such third party, provided such third party agrees to observe this Privacy Policy. Www.orlygift.com may change this Privacy Policy from time to time to accurately reflect how we gather and manage User information. 

We will post any changes to this Privacy Policy on the Website and, where appropriate and practicable, notify you by e-mail. All changes to the Privacy Policy will be effective upon posting to the Website. Please be sure to regularly check our Privacy Policy before using the Website. Continued use of the Website shall indicate your acceptance of any changes to this Privacy Policy. 

**Disclaimer**

The information provided in this Privacy Policy should not be construed as giving business, legal or other advice, or warranting as fail proof the integrity and security of information provided through this Website. While all reasonable attempts are made to provide accurate, current and reliable information, Www.orlygift.com recognizes the possibility of human and/or mechanical error and the possibility that Users of the Site and other third parties may provide and/or publish information, graphics and images on the Site that are false, misleading, or inaccurate. 

Therefore, Www.orlygift.com makes no representations as to the accuracy, completeness, currency or suitability of the information provided on this Website, and denies any expressed or implied warranty as to the same. For further disclaimers and limitations of liability of Www.orlygift.com regarding your use of the Website and Service, see its Terms of Service. 

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service provider’s utilized and other similar information. 

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly. 

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. 

We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission. 

**Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. 

These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies. 

**Use of Location Based-Services**

ORLYGIFT and its partners and licensors may provide certain features or services through the Service that rely upon device-based location information. To provide such features or services, where available, ORLYGIFT and its partners and licensors may collect, use, transmit, process and maintain your location data, including the real-time geographic location of your device, and you hereby agree and consent to ORLYGIFT 's and its partners' and licensors' collection, use, transmission, processing and maintenance of such location data to provide such services. In addition, by enabling and/or using any location-based services or features within the Service, you agree and consent to ORLYGIFT collecting, using, processing and maintaining information related to your account, and any devices registered thereunder, for purposes of providing such location-based service or feature to you. Such information may include, but is not limited to, your device ID and name, device type and real-time geographic location of your device at time of your request. You may withdraw this consent at any time by not using the location-based features on your device. When using third party services that use or provide location data as part of the Service, you are subject to and should review such third party's terms and privacy policy on use of location data by such third party services. Any location data provided by the Service is not intended to be relied upon in situations where precise location information is needed or where erroneous, inaccurate, time-delayed or incomplete location data may lead to death, personal injury, property or environmental damage. Neither ORLYGIFT nor any of its content providers guarantees the availability, accuracy, completeness, reliability, or timeliness of location data or any other data displayed by the Service. 

**Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. 

This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. Since this is an informational blog, humor blog, parody website you have the opportunity to place ads or advertisements with us, please contact our support team for more information. 

**Mouseflow**

This website uses Mouseflow, a web analysis tool of Mouseflow ApS, Flaesketorvet 68, 1711 Copenhagen, Denmark, to collect and store data for marketing and optimization purposes. From the data, pseudonymised usage profiles can be created. Randomly selected individual visits (only with anonymous IP address) are recorded. The result is a log of mouse movements and clicks with the intention of randomly sampling individual website visits and deriving potential improvements for the website. The data collected by Mouseflow will not be used to personally identify the visitor to this website and will not be merged with personal data about the bearer of the pseudonym without the specific consent of the data subject. If you do not want a recording, you can globally disable a recording on all websites that use Mouseflow for your current browser at https://mouseflow.com/opt-out 

**Choice/Opt-out**

If we ever send you information by email concerning new products, services or information that you did not expressly request, we will provide you with an email address by which you may request no further notices. 

**Compliance with children’s online privacy protection act**

www.orlygift.com understands Google along with all other web browsers must adhere to any and all laws, of any and all States with the United States and abroad when anyone under the age of 18 years old is involved. www.orlygift.com is law compliant. Www.orlygift.com does not hire children to perform any work on this web property or for the company itself. Children are not allowed to peruse, join, read, write or co-join this website. 

Children is defined as a person under the age of 18 years age, no matter if they are emancipated or not, or they are the ward of court jurisdictions. Children are not allowed to contract, therefore, may not purchase services and or products from www.orlygift.com. 

**CAN SPAM Act**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations. 

We collect your email address in order to: 

  * Send information; respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
  * Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders
  * We may also send you additional information related to your product and/or service
  * Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred

To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:

  * NOT use false or misleading subjects or email addresses
  * Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way
  * Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters
  * Monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used
  * Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly
  * Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email

**Fair Information Practices**

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information. 

**In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:**

  * We will notify the users via email within 7 business days.
  * We will notify the users via in site notification within 7 business days

We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only those individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors. 

**Changes to this privacy policy**

www.orlygift.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. 

You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications. 

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and Terms of Service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. 

**Contact us**

Orlygift welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy.   
If you believe that Orlygift has not adhered to this Statement, please contact us at:
